<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
     xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
     >
  <channel>
    <title>Random Thoughts and Geekery</title>
    <link>http://www.antzucaro.com</link>
    <description>The musings and ramblings of Ant Zucaro</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 14:21:40 GMT</pubDate>
    <generator>Blogofile</generator>
    <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
    <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
    <item>
      <title>Grandpa's Garage</title>
      <link>http://www.antzucaro.com/2010/12/grandpas-garage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 18:52:49 EST</pubDate>
      <category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[life]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[wandering around]]></category>
      <guid>http://www.antzucaro.com/?p=563</guid>
      <description>Grandpa's Garage</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104704.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-564" title="Grandpa's Garage" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104704-1024x764.jpg" alt="Grandpa's Garage" width="450" height="335" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Grandpa&#39;s Garage</p></div>

<p>Over Thanksgiving holiday I got the chance to briefly hang out at my grandmother's house on Long Island. It felt great to have no work obligations and to just take in the house with the family. One thing I especially like to do when I'm there is to wander around my grandfather's garage.</p>
<p>Grandpa died seven years ago this month, but his spirit still resides in that garage. It's partly the endless clutter of things (which it seems he saved just for savings sake) and partly the smell of grease and long-gone wood shavings from his work that make it seem special. It's also just neat seeing all of the old hardware and parts for things waiting to be fixed. Rest assured that if anything ever breaks in grandma's house, she'll have a part to fix it at the ready! What's more is that grandpa probably found that part in someones junk, was given the part for free, or otherwise obtained it outside of a store.</p>
<p>This drawer unit was probably tossed out by his office building when he was working there. Rather than let it go to some dumpster or removal service, he found service for it in the garage (for about 30 years at that):</p>
<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104202.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-565" title="Drawers" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104202-1024x764.jpg" alt="Drawers" width="450" height="335" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Drawers</p></div>

<p>Here's what looks like a repurposed work desk. I don't have any guesses about this one, but you can tell from its worn paint and scratches throughout that it received a lot of love:</p>
<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104457.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-566" title="Work bench" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104457-1024x764.jpg" alt="Work bench" width="450" height="335" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Work bench</p></div>

<p>Here's a set of screwdrivers sitting in manually-drilled holes in a 2x4. Thrifty! Sorry for the blur:</p>
<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104533.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-567" title="Screwdrivers" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104533-1024x764.jpg" alt="Screwdrivers" width="450" height="335" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Screwdrivers</p></div>

<p>Here's a paper towel dispenser mounted on the wall. What I think is cool are those magnets for holding the pencils and pens - I use that same concept on my fridge, albeit with more geeky elements (hard drive magnets)!</p>
<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104610-e1292111068477.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-568" title="Paper towel dispenser" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104610-e1292111068477-764x1024.jpg" alt="Paper towel dispenser" width="450" height="603" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Paper towel dispenser</p></div>

<p>Here's a funny assortment of clips:</p>
<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104720.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-569" title="Assorted spring-loaded clips" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104720-e1292111229855-764x1024.jpg" alt="Assorted spring-loaded clips" width="450" height="603" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Assorted spring-loaded clips</p></div>

<p>...and more spare buckets than you can shake a stick at. Hey, you never know when you need to wash 50 cars at once!</p>
<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104803.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-570" title="That's a lotta buckets" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104803-e1292111288176-764x1024.jpg" alt="That's a lotta buckets" width="450" height="603" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">That&#39;s a lotta buckets</p></div>

<p>Dust-laden cans from who knows how long ago. Note the collection of dust:</p>
<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104843.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-571" title="Cans from who knows when" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/12/IMG_20101127_104843-e1292111349726-764x1024.jpg" alt="Cans from who knows when" width="450" height="603" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Cans from who knows when</p></div>

<p>The way grandpa lived his life left impressions on all of us in the family, with some impressions being more subtle than the others. As I was cleaning out a jar of pasta sauce the other day, I noticed that it had measurement markings built into the the glass for cups and ounces. I thought to myself "free measuring cup!" and started to clean it off to put in the cupboard. That's grandpa's mentality at work! My wife politely pointed out that we already had two measuring cups and that we had no need for a third, jury-rigged one. Although it was tough to put that jar in the recycling bin, I had to agree with that logic. Maybe I would have felt differently if I had a fantastic garage, like grandpa, in which to store such things!</p>
<p>ï»¿</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>http://www.antzucaro.com/2010/11/new-york-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 09:50:27 EST</pubDate>
      <category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[life]]></category>
      <guid>http://www.antzucaro.com/?p=531</guid>
      <description>New York Thanksgiving</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img style="display:block;margin-right:auto;margin-left:auto;" alt="image" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/11/wpid-IMG_20101126_094406.jpg" />

<p>How's this for efficiency? Turn around, kneel a bit, strap those packs on, and you're gone!</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here comes winter</title>
      <link>http://www.antzucaro.com/2010/11/here-comes-winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 08:50:20 EST</pubDate>
      <category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[life]]></category>
      <guid>http://www.antzucaro.com/?p=526</guid>
      <description>Here comes winter</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As I look down at my desktop calendar, I'm completely surprised that it's the end of November <em>already</em>. Time truly does fly when you're having fun, and apparently even more so when you are having fun with an infant!</p>
<p>Kristin doesn't welcome the upcoming winter season, but I certainly do. The different season really gives the days a new feel for me, given that it is dark when I leave for work <em>and</em> when I come home. One benefit of this is getting to see the Reston Town Center skyline as I head out the office door - it makes me feel like I work in Manhatten, as opposed to the 6 square blocks (or so) of RTC:</p>
<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 450px"><a href="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/11/RTC_nov.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-527" title="The view of the SW corner of RTC" src="http://media.antzucaro.com/uploads/2010/11/RTC_nov-1024x764.jpg" alt="The view of the SW corner of RTC" width="450" height="335" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">The view of the SW corner of RTC</p></div>

<p>Granted, the downside is that it's starting to get really cold. In fact, The DC area doesn't seem to have much of a fall season at all - we just go from 90 degree weather down to 40s in a span of two weeks. That's okay, though. I can always put on more layers as the mercury levels drop, whereas in the summer it isn't as socially acceptable to remove too many layers :).</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being a Parent</title>
      <link>http://www.antzucaro.com/2010/07/being-a-parent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 06:52:12 EDT</pubDate>
      <category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[life]]></category>
      <guid>http://www.antzucaro.com/?p=244</guid>
      <description>Being a Parent</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"></p>

<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 500px"><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/cataldo/"><img class="     " title="Baby next to diapers" src="http://farm1.static.flickr.com/34/116811768_ed57f12c16.jpg" alt="" width="500" height="333" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Image courtesy of Aldo Risolvo on Flickr</p></div>

<p>Sometimes simply being a parent takes up your day. Yesterday was one such day, when Layla needed constant attention after being awake for a marathon-like (for her) 5 1/2 hours. After playing in the mirror, hanging out in the high chair, and swinging in the swing, she just wanted more! I'd look over at her in the crib after she'd tricked me into thinking she was tired, only to find a big toothless smile and happy eyes looking back at me. What a cutie!</p>
<p>My first reaction after several iterations of this was frustration, but this soon gave way to feelings of guilt. After all, these are the days that I should cherish! Soon she'll be crawling and thereafter will start becoming more and more independent each day. That means what I have right now is so, so special. Having realized that yesterday towards the end of my (our?) ordeal, those feelings of frustration melted away, leaving me there to soak up the experience for what it was.</p>
<p>I have several hobbies - photography, running, Linux, and (ahem) this blog - but none of them are as important as my daughter. I need to remind myself of that each time I complain to myself or someone else about my struggles with parenting. My role as a dad could very well be the most important one in my life! Everything else fades in comparison, and that is the way it is supposed to be.</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mindful Running Hacks</title>
      <link>http://www.antzucaro.com/2010/07/mindful-running-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 13:13:32 EDT</pubDate>
      <category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[life]]></category>
      <guid>http://blog.antzucaro.com/?p=204</guid>
      <description>Mindful Running Hacks</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="wp-caption aligncenter" style="width: 640px"><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rcsaxon/542566756/"><img title="Runners" src="http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1351/542566756_db45e39778_z.jpg" alt="Runners" width="640" height="480" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Image courtesy of Richard Saxon</p></div>

<p>I love running; I'm a runner. On weekends, early in the morning, and even during my ever-decreasing lunch breaks, I run. I feel like it gives me the clairvoyance needed to tackle whatever problems I'm having in my life at the moment. As an example, right now I mostly focus on how to solve programming problems by putting them on the back-burner of my mind while my feet hit the pavement repeatedly. It's therapeutic! It's also a huge benefit to your body, but I don't have to tell you that, right? There are a few problems that I have to consider when running, though. Long distance running can be a mind game in which winning means enjoying your run and losing means experiencing pure agony for each centimeter traveled. This post is about handling that mind game.</p>
<p>Let me start by saying that long distance running is completely relative to each person and their experience. I'm sure "long run" to <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alberto_Salazar">Alberto Salazaar</a> means 20+ miles in a single stretch. It can be relative on other things, too - 5 mile runs seem much longer when you are running in 90 degree, 80% humidity weather, don't they! For purposes of this post my "long" runs are those of 5 miles or longer only because that seems to be a sweet spot.</p>
<p>So here's the thing: when I'm running long distances, I tend to psych myself out when I think too much about how my body is performing. I get into an endless loop of assessment similar to the following:
<ul>
    <li>How is my breathing - is it too rapid, too conversational?</li>
    <li>How is the "chaffage" situation - are my armpits, legs, etc uncomfortable?</li>
    <li>Am I getting enough water, carbs?</li>
    <li>How am I doing on my target pace?</li>
</ul>
While certainly useful in a long race, this constant checking and re-checking makes me <strong>too aware</strong> of any degradations in my performance. Translation: by constantly assessing myself, I find that I actually decrease my performance. Not good! To remedy this self-imposed issue, I employ one or more of the following "mindful running hacks" to keep my mind in check and to get more enjoyment out of my runs. I call them mind<em><strong>ful</strong></em> because they don't really involve your physical self; these things deal exclusively with the battles you can have inside your mind when running long distances. Anyway, here goes...
<ol>
    <li>
<h3><strong>Establish a mantra</strong></h3>
</li>
</ol>
A mantra is something - a phrase, song, word - that you repeat over and over either physically or mentally to occupy your mind's conscious thoughts; it's really just a big distraction, not at all unlike when you think about your summer vacation (or other happy times) when you are in the dentist's chair. I use mantras to zone out when running. I tend to go with some sort of positive or realistic phrase pertinent to my route. Examples:
<ul>
    <li>This is how I'm <em>supposed </em>to feel</li>
    <li>&lt;insert some lyrics of a song I've been listening to here&gt;</li>
    <li>Calm, cool, collected, <em>confident</em></li>
    <li>X (substitute X with whatever mile/km you are currently on)</li>
</ul>
I find they are effective as such, but relatively boring overall. This means that the longer my run is, the less likely I am to utilize this one. I have to break up the monotony, which leads me to my next point.
<h3><strong>2. Break up the run into chunks</strong></h3>
I break down my long runs into manageable chunks, and I only focusing on one chunk at a time. In the middle of my 10 mile run, I think about the plethora of other 5 mile runs I've completed with no problem. I will myself to forget the miles that are increasingly behind me - what's left is what matters, and what's left is shrinking with each step! I find that I break down my runs into roughly half-mile increments. That's probably a byproduct of my watch's capacity to store lap information, but you can use whatever works for you.
<h3><strong>3. Positive thinking, visualization</strong></h3>
I know, it sounds lame. But if it is <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Cant-Accept-Not-Trying-Excellence/dp/0062511904/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8&amp;s=books&amp;qid=1278002864&amp;sr=8-3">good enough for Michael Jordan</a>, why shouldn't it be good enough for me? I envision my run before and during my actual run. This helps me anticipate how I am going to physically feel as I take step after step. Knowing what to expect mid-race makes me feel more in control, thus boosting my confidence. What I do is think mostly about how my body is going to handle the most difficult portions of a given route - that big up/downhill, the slippery rock or dirt section, etc.  - then I play that section in my head over and over. With repetition comes boredom, so when I actually encounter the obstacle I've been thinking about it doesn't seem so bad.
<h3><strong>4. Use Jeff Galloway's "dirty tricks"</strong></h3>
I have a book called <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Marathon-You-Can-Jeff-Galloway/dp/0936070250">"Marathon: You Can Do It!" by Jeff Galloway</a>, the running guru. In it he provides a couple of mind techniques to use that he calls "dirty tricks." All of them are more or less distraction techniques, but I want to bear mention of them here. I've tried each with success, although with a slight bit of embarrassment. The good thing is that no one has to know - it's all in your head!:
<ul>
    <li>Pretend that you and the person in front of you are lashed together with a giant rubber band. Envision the tension of that rubber band is propelling your body forward and past your opponent.</li>
    <li>In an effort to decrease the influence of the right brain when running (which seems to be the dominant half when doing so, for some reason), do math or other analytical (non-logic) problems that help engage your left brain. The idea is to shift the balance between your left and right brains to keep your mind fresh.</li>
    <li>Imagine a giant hand is guiding you through the difficult parts of the race, gently pushing you so as to relieve part of your strain.</li>
    <li>Glide vs. Stride - switch up your stride every once in a while. Go from short, choppy strides to long ones where your feet barely clear the ground. Note: this one isn't just a mental trick. The physical changes help your muscles go longer.</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>5. Get Angry</strong></h3>
When I really can't get myself into gear, I imagine things that make me angry. I envision all of my friends laughing at my speed (or lack thereof) or I replay an embarrassing incident in my life. When I do this I feel the immediate need to improve; to prove that those incidents are behind me and I am now a better person. Really though, I tend to use this as a last resort because it is negative thinking.
<h3><strong>In conclusion...</strong></h3>
So there you have it - my list of things I use to make my runs less mind-numbingly difficult. I find that if I use the things I've mentioned here my long runs (those of 5 or more miles, but your YMMV) become enjoyable because I'm not endlessly diagnosing myself and my performance. Rather, I'm focusing on generally positive thoughts or distracting myself altogether. Either way I see a net benefit in becoming more fit and enjoying it all the while!</p>
<p>What do <em><strong>you </strong></em>do to make your runs better? I'd like to know!</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeping your sanity with an infant</title>
      <link>http://www.antzucaro.com/2010/06/keeping-your-sanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 12:10:58 EDT</pubDate>
      <category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[life]]></category>
      <guid>http://blog.antzucaro.com/?p=177</guid>
      <description>Keeping your sanity with an infant</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em></em>Those of you who know me personally also know that I had a baby girl this past Easter (Layla, on 4/4). It has been a tiring, stressful, and <em>totally wonderful</em> experience! What I'd like to talk about specifically are the first two points (the tiring and the stressful) and four things I've learned to cope with them. I hope these things will benefit you. If they do, great! If not...well, forget about everything I said and go about doing whatever it was you were going to do anyway :). Here goes...
<h3>1. Sleep when baby sleeps</h3>
When my little girl is crying, my ability to properly diagnose the situation almost entirely depends on how rested I am. I know that the more rested I am, the more clear mind mind will be. Is she hungry? Is she too hot? Does she have gas? I'll never figure it out if my mind is too cloudy. That means it is extremely important for me to get as much sleep as I can.</p>
<p>Therein lies the problem - you don't have much time for sleep. At least I thought I didn't at first. I learned after a few hard weeks that I had to lay down and sleep when Layla went down, else I wouldn't be sleeping at all. Surprisingly, the amount of sleep I was getting after a few weeks of doing this increased dramatically because I was better able to handle/fix whatever was bothering Layla. She'd been giving me the signs all along (turning her head when hungry, kicking her legs when gassy, etc) and I'd just been to tired (or too dumb) to pay attention. Addressing those issues quickly and correctly calmed her down and prevented "meltdowns," which then increased her snooze-time.
<h3><strong>2. Make connections with other people in your same situation</strong></h3>
My wife and I felt alone in the first few weeks after Layla was born. None of our close friends had newborns and we didnâ€™t feel comfortable going to a â€œmommyâ€ or â€œdaddyâ€ meetup in our city. We eventually sucked it up and started scheduling lunches and dinners with other parents who weâ€™d met through mutual friends or work. We figure that doing this created win-win situations for us: we get to talk with people who experience the same issues while making new friends at the same time. Who wouldâ€™ve thought (duh, right)? Plus, I developed a bunch of ideas (or avoided roadblocks altogether) through conversations with these new friends. They really are wonderful exchanges, with each side of the table contributing something or other that makes life with an infant just a little bit easier.</p>
<p>I think all it took was that little connection with the outside world to make us feel like we were still part of something, instead of feeling like we were on an uninhabited island where no one else had kids.
<h3>3. Change up your scenery</h3>
This really goes without saying, but I feel I have to say it anyway: you <strong>have</strong> to change up your surroundings or else you are going to go insane. I am especially prone to cabin fever, but it seemed amplified knowing you have the weight of another human relying on  you 100% on your shoulders. For whatever reason, Kristin and I stayed in the house more often than not. I donâ€™t know what it was that kept us there for so long, but after a while we grew determined to make it easier to go out and about. We critically analyzed our process management science style, which resulted in the following decisions:
<ul>
    <li>We opted against a traditional diaper bag, going with a backpack instead. We already owned a backpack (diaper bags are not cheap, by the way), and it allowed us to have two arms totally free to handle other things.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
    <li>We got a portable changing pad like this [http://www.walmart.com/ip/Summer-Infant-ChangeAway-Portable-Changing-Pad-Diaper-Kit/12960886?sourceid=1500000000000003260330&amp;ci_src=14110944&amp;ci_sku=12960886]  and pre-populated it with all of the change stuff weâ€™d need.</li>
    <li>We bought a different, lighter weight stroller for the "quick trips" out. We love our Chicco, but it gets left at home when we're heading to the mall.</li>
    <li>Formula! We used to keep those freezer packs in our bag to keep the milk cold. Nowadays we just bring a pre-measured amount of formula along with bottles with the corresponding amount of water. Hungry baby? Mix, shake, and your done. Many thanks to our neighbors who let us borrow a <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Sassy-Powdered-Formula-Dispenser-Multiple/dp/B000067PIZ/ref=pd_sbs_misc_2">tupperware formula thingamajig</a> to dispense the formula powder in the least messy fashion.</li>
</ul>
With these changes made, getting out of the house wasn't such a big deal any more. Hooray!
<h3>4. Make daily goals for yourself</h3>
Nothing feels better than checking things off of your TODO list. What I do is make little lists with what I want to accomplish during the day. These become my daily goals which made me feel good about my day when completed. Take note  - these aren't mind-bendingly awesome goals or long term in any way, but rather simple things that moved my new life further a little bit at a time:
<ul>
    <li>Folding the laundry (ugh, what a dreaded task)</li>
    <li>Calling back a friend</li>
    <li>De-cluttering my desk</li>
</ul>
As Bill Murray says in <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0103241/">What About Bob?</a>: baby steps, baby steps! Checking off those baby steps - no matter how little -  feels <em><strong>good</strong></em>.</p>
<p>So that's what I've done; these four things have helped me transition to being a parent. Babies are stressful, but awesome (especially if you can decrease that stressful part).</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm Back</title>
      <link>http://www.antzucaro.com/2010/02/imback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 17:35:46 EST</pubDate>
      <category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[life]]></category>
      <guid>http://localhost/afzphotowp/?p=33</guid>
      <description>I'm Back</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi everyone!</p>
<p>I've been away from this little internet space for about two and a half years. Sorry about that. In my own defense, I was in grad school, purchasing a house, quitting jobs, finding other jobs, and watching movies (lots of movies). My goal from now on is to add content to this site regularly as a means to express myself and to own my own content. I'll be posting under a couple of categories, the first two being "blog" and "galleries." They mean exactly what you think they mean - a "blog" category post means a post contains the ramblings of my brain/personal opinion, howtos, geek stuff, etc etc. The "galleries" category means the post will be used to post my images. Simple, right? Right. I hope you enjoy.</p>
<p>I am still deciding what to do with all of the older content (from college and what has been stagnant for the past 2.5 years). I may re-post, but who knows.</p>
<p>-Ant</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
